<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UNICEF Job Vacancies (Filtered)</title>
    <link>https://jobs.unicef.org/</link>
    <description>Filtered UNICEF job vacancies: Professional (P-1 to P-5), Director (D-1/D-2), internships and fellowships.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2026 07:49:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <atom:link href="https://cinfoposte.github.io/unicef-jobs/unicef_jobs.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>JPO-Education Officer (digital learning), P-2, Luanda/Angola (For Finnish Nationals only)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591370</link>
      <description>JPO Education Officer (Digital Learning), P-2, Luanda, Angola.

Join UNICEF Angola as a Junior Professional Officer (JPO) – Education Officer (Digital Learning) and help accelerate innovative learning solutions that reach every child. This P‑2 role, funded by the Government of Finland, offers an exceptional opportunity for a motivated early‑career professional to contribute to high-impact digital learning initiatives in one of UNICEF’s priority countries.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1573889894488314</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovation Specialist (Market Scoping), P-3, Systems &amp; Services, Office of Innovation, Temporary Appointment (364 days), #00136398</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591374</link>
      <description>Join UNICEF’s Office of Innovation as an Innovation Specialist (Market Scoping) and help connect the world’s most promising innovations to challenges facing children globally. Based in Stockholm, this role leads market intelligence and ecosystem scanning efforts, leveraging AI-enabled tools and global partnerships to identify, assess, and accelerate scalable solutions across startups, academia, and the private sector to drive impact at scale</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1172516949527578</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gender &amp; Adolescent Programme Officer – Temporary appointment – 364 days - Grade P2 # 136135- Cotonou – Benin WCAR</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591378</link>
      <description>Benin is a middle-income country that faces many challenges in guaranteeing the rights of every child. Ranked 158th out of 191 countries on the Human Development Index (UNDP, 2021/2022), it has significant disparities between urban and rural areas, and between girls and boys. Since 1977, UNICEF has been working closely with the government, civil society, technical and financial partners, young people and communities to improve access to education, health services, protection, water, sanitation, nutrition and social policies for children.
The 2024-2026 cooperation program pays particular attention to girls' education, protection against violence, community health, and the fight against child labor. Present in the field through its offices in Cotonou, Natitingou and Parakou, UNICEF is committed to working alongside the most vulnerable communities to guarantee concrete, lasting results.
The UNICEF Benin office is looking for committed, creative and motivated professionals to make a difference in the life of every Beninese child.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3170679556645823</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programme Manager, P-3, Panama Country Office, Panama City (8 months) #136527</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591359</link>
      <description>The Programme Manager reports to the Country Office (CO) Representative for general supervision and direction. The Programme Manager supports the Representative on the overall management of the CO and coordinating closely with the different sections on all phases of the Country Programme, from formulation to delivery of results in accordance with UNICEF Strategic Plans, standards of performance and accountability framework, ethics and integrity.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1925951562905830</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH Officer, (P2), La Paz-Bolivia, # 136480 (Temporary Appointment)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591311</link>
      <description>Are you seeking an opportunity to contribute to the affairs of children, their protection and development? If you fit the call above, don’t miss this exciting offer at UNICEF Bolivia.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1009124959111089</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 15:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Manager, (P-4), Temporary Position, 364 days, #00136265, Office of Strategy &amp; Evidence (OSE) - Innocenti, Florence, Italy</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591309</link>
      <description>Join UNICEF’s Data Transformation &amp; Enabling AI Initiative to help build a smarter, more data‑informed organization. Support the end-to-end transformation that strengthens data governance, improves data quality, and enables responsible AI adoption. Drive measurable impact by delivering skilled and effective project management.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2107447906664405</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senior Adviser - Recovery, P-5, Temporary Position, Programme Group, 6 months, Global Programme Division - PSCH, Outposted in Rome #00136399 (Remote)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591313</link>
      <description>Technical Assistance to Country Offices Provide technical support to designated or transitioning L2/L3 Country Offices in child‑focused recovery planning and programme design, including adapting recovery tools and participating in joint missions. Maintain and coordinate a roster of recovery specialists.Multistakeholder Recovery Assessment and Planning Support national and multistakeholder recovery assessments and frameworks to ensure children’s and women’s needs and rights are integrated into planning, budgeting, service delivery, and recovery financing strategies.Focused Support to State of Palestine and Syria Refine UNICEF recovery strategies, identify technical and operational requirements, and support Programme Budget Reviews, Strategic Moments of Reflection, and annual programme reviews. Liaise with interagency partners, donors, and global mechanisms to promote coherence in recovery assessment, planning, and financing.Global Coordination and Positioning Represent UNICEF in global mechanisms related to recovery assessment and planning, contribute to interagency policy, tools, and standards, and support whole‑of‑house coordination on recovery</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1075259453388861</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internship: Partnership and Knowledge Management Intern, UNICEF Global Learning Innovation Hub - Helsinki, Finland, 6 months (In person preferred/full time)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591275</link>
      <description>The UNICEF Global Learning Innovation Hub in Helsinki is seeking a Partnership and Knowledge Management Intern to support both partnerships and knowledge management functions, with a particular focus on digital education and learning innovation. The internship is designed as a learning-focused role for a recent graduate or early-career professional and offers an opportunity to gain hands-on experience in international development, partnerships, and digital education programming within a global team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1653340466298350</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project Specialist (Data Governance), (P-3), TA, #00136405, Office of Strategy &amp; Evidence (OSE) - Innocenti, Florence, Italy</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591274</link>
      <description>Join UNICEF’s Data Transformation Initiative (DTI) to help build a more efficient, data‑informed organization by championing strong data governance standards, guiding the development of robust governance frameworks, and driving the successful implementation of data practices that enhance data quality, reduce inefficiencies, enable innovation—including AI readiness—and strengthen the organization’s ability to manage key data risks.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2382878349824385</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cold Chain Specialist, P-3, Temporary Position, 364 days, Bujumbura, Burundi, #00136435</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591277</link>
      <description>UNICEF Burundi is seeking qualified candidates to lead and strengthen national immunization logistics by managing cold chain operations, vaccine forecasting, and deployment across all levels of the health system. This role also provides training and field mentoring to ensure high‑quality EPI performance and effective implementation of the country’s vaccine management strategies.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2197283910533990</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>People and Culture Specialist, (P-3), Regional Office, Amman-Jordan, Post#127035, Temporary Appointment for 8 months</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591260</link>
      <description>The P&amp;C Specialist, within their area of responsibility, is accountable for implementing HR services that enhance the capacity of their clients to deliver on their business goals and objectives. In doing so, the incumbent demonstrates the ability to anticipate HR-related needs and develop subsequent plans and solutions that align HR management with business objectives, particularly in supporting the different ongoing emergencies in the region. The incumbent will be the designated focal point for basic HR emergency support, ensuring timely recruitment, onboarding, and deployment of personnel during crisis situations. The incumbent will also support the regional office and country offices’ emergency preparedness.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2551203387217043</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovation Specialist (Innovative Financing, Outcome-Based Financing), (P-3) TA (until 31 December 2026), # 136476, Innovative &amp; Alternative Financ Children, PFP, Geneva, Switzerland</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591224</link>
      <description>UNICEF has set out ambitious goals for its 2026-2029 Strategic Plan to accelerate progress towards achieving the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The Division of Private Fundraising and Partnerships (PFP), based in Geneva, aims to achieve results for children by maximizing UNICEF's private sector fundraising, partnerships and engagement activities, including work with National Committees, regional and country offices, and other HQ Divisions.

The global innovative financing for children (IF4C) initiative is key to UNICEF's Strategic Plan 2026-2029 and resource mobilization strategy and aims to help address complex global challenges such as climate change and disasters, faced by millions of children and adolescents today and disproportionately affecting the poorest, most vulnerable, and marginalized.

The PFP IF4C team enables, drives, and accelerates innovative alternative financing and funding solutions for children in partnership with the Private Sector through initiatives that attract investments for climate change, environment, and disaster risk reduction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2078209525142125</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Innovation Specialist (Innovative Financing, Sovereign Debt Solutions) (P-3) TA (until 31 December 2026), # 136477, Innovative &amp; Alternative Finance Children, PFP, Geneva, Switzerland</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591226</link>
      <description>UNICEF has set out ambitious goals for its 2026-2029 Strategic Plan to accelerate progress towards achieving the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs). The Division of Private Fundraising and Partnerships (PFP), based in Geneva, aims to achieve results for children by maximizing UNICEF's private sector fundraising, partnerships and engagement activities, including work with National Committees, regional and country offices, and other HQ Divisions.

The global innovative financing for children (IF4C) initiative is key to UNICEF's Strategic Plan 2026-2029 and resource mobilization strategy and aims to help address complex global challenges such as climate change and disasters, faced by millions of children and adolescents today and disproportionately affecting the poorest, most vulnerable, and marginalized.

The PFP IF4C team enables, drives, and accelerates innovative alternative financing and funding solutions for children in partnership with the Private Sector through initiatives that attract investments for climate change, environment, and disaster risk reduction.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2616816628782530</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Child Protection Officer, (P-2), Accra, Ghana (Junior Professional Officer Position)-Open to Norwegian nationals only</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/590983</link>
      <description>UNICEF Ghana is seeking a dynamic Child Protection Officer to join our team. The Officer will provide technical and coordination support to integrate climate change adaptation, disaster risk reduction, and humanitarian–development linkages into national child protection systems. The assignment will contribute to evidence generation, systems strengthening, and preparedness efforts that reduce inequalities, protect vulnerable children, and enhance the resilience of social welfare and child protection services in Ghana. This is a Junior Professional Officer (JPO) position. Opportunity is open to Norwegian nationals only.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2528151702488335</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vacancy Announcement- Education Specialist, P-3, TA, 364 Days, Kano, Nigeria #136413</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591177</link>
      <description>UNICEF Nigeria Field Office in Kano, Nigeria is seeking a passionate and committed person to work in the role of an Education Specialist and invites applications from highly motivated and committed persons who want to contribute to results for children. If you are that person, we encourage you to apply and become part of a highly motivated and committed team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2619498178934803</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chief, Liquidity Management, P-5, Fixed Term Position, DFAM, Treasury and Structured Finance Services, New York, USA #00008215</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591176</link>
      <description>This is a NYHQ position in the Treasury and Structured Finance Section under the Division of Finance and Administrative Management (DFAM) reporting to the Deputy Director D1 level. The incumbent will lead the Liquidity Management Unit which provides timely and efficient execution of all treasury payments as well as treasury accounting matters to ensure data integrity is refeleted in the financial statements.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3230271814370527</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WASH Manager, (P-4), Maiduguri Nigeria #136389 [Temp Appointment]</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591108</link>
      <description>UNICEF Nigeria Country Office, Nigeria is seeking a passionate and committed person to work in the role of a WASH Manager and invites applications from highly motivated and committed persons who want to contribute to results for children. If you are that person, we encourage you to apply and become part of a highly motivated and committed team</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">2158423736544844</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education Specialist (Early Childhood Education), P3, Dili, Timor-Leste, #136263 (Temporary Appointment)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591083</link>
      <description>Join our UNICEF Timor-Leste team and help shape a better future for every child. Under the guidance and general supervision of the Chief Education, the Education Specialist provide support on the programme preparation, planning and implementation, contributes to the achievement of sustainable results to improve learning outcomes and universal access to quality, equitable and inclusive education. Success in education programmes and projects in turn contribute to maintaining and enhancing the credibility and ability of UNICEF to provide programme services for mothers and children that promotes greater social equality in the country.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">3021355388205240</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Re-advertisement: Market Research Specialist, P-3, Fixed Term Position, O/P Panama City, Panama, Audience &amp; Market Insights, PFP #00134108</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/583442</link>
      <description>UNICEF is looking for Market Research Specialist who drives an audience-informed approach across private-sector fundraising and partnerships in the Americas, while contributing to AMI's global insight streams. Partnering and consulting with teams across Communications, Fundraising and Advocacy to:
1. Listening &amp; scope - surface stakeholder objectives and translate them into clear insight plans
2. Planning &amp; execution - deploy the right blend of qualitative and quantitative methods (e.g., ethnography, focus groups, surveys, depths, media analysis) to address each need.
3. Synthesize &amp; interpret - turn data into compelling narratives and concrete, actionable recommendations.
4. Drive uptake - package findings through workshops, briefs and tools that help teams act decisively on the insights.
5. Collaborate globally - align methodologies and share learnings with peer specialists and managers in Latin America, Europe, and HQ to ensure consistency and cross-pollination of best practice.
6. Evaluation - ensure team's feedback on the effectiveness or not of the insight solutions, both for AMI's accountability and to ensure lessons can be brought into the team.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">5230344917622709</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design &amp; Branding Intern, Amman, Jordan Country Office, (3 months), Full time on-site, (Open for Jordanian Nationals Only)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/591067</link>
      <description>UNICEF Jordan Country Office is seeking to hire a passionate, dynamic, and collaborative Design&amp; Branding Intern , to support the Communications &amp; Advocacy team. The intern will contribute to visual storytelling, brand consistency, and creative assets across digital, print, and internal communication platforms, supporting UNICEF’s programmes and partnerships in Jordan.</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1190805819118062</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPO WASH Officer, P-2, Gaza, State of Palestine (Open to Dutch Nationals Only)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/589328</link>
      <description>If you are a committed, creative professional and you would like to make an active and lasting contribution to build a better and safe world for children, we would like to hear from you. The State of Palestine office is seeking a dynamic qualified candidate to join our team as a JPO WASH Officer at the P-2 level based in the Gaza Strip, SOP.

The position is open in the context of the Junior Professional Officer (JPO) scheme sponsored by the Government of the Netherlands and is addressed exclusively to candidates with the DUTCH NATIONALITY ONLY. 

For the minimum qualification requirements see the website of Nedworc Foundation: 
https://nedworcfoundation.nl/junior-professional-officers-programme/

The maximum age limit is 32 years as of 31 December of the year of application.

Please read the criteria and FAQ section carefully before considering applying</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1738473265357071</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPO Emergency Officer, P-2, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia (Open to nationals of eligible developing countries only)</title>
      <link>https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en-us/job/589340</link>
      <description>Join our team to develop and strengthen emergency preparedness plans, conduct risk assessments, and contingency planning. These efforts help increase the resilience of affected communities and improve their capacity to respond effectively to crises. The JPO also ensures that emergency responses are well-coordinated, preventing duplication of efforts and maximizing the use of resources.

This post is opened in the context of the Junior Professional Officer (JPO) scheme sponsored by the Government of the Netherlands and is addressed exclusively to the CANDIDATES WITH THE NATIONALITY OF ONE OF THE FOLLOWING ELIGIBLE COUNTRIES, excluding Ethiopia, due to the restriction that nationals of the country where the position is located cannot be considered: https://nedworcfoundation.nl/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/eligible-countries-DC-JPOs-2025.pdf

For the minimum qualification requirements see the website of Nedworc Foundation: 
https://nedworcfoundation.nl/junior-professional-officers-programme/
 
The maximum age limit is 32 years as of 31 December of the year of application.

Please read the selection criteria and FAQ section carefully before considering applying</description>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">8503073742715370</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <source url="https://careers.pageuppeople.com/671/cw/en/rss">UNICEF Careers RSS</source>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>